Sex Work. Survival. Sisterhood.
The Stroll is a documentary film directed by Kristen Parker Lovell.
The history of New York’s Meatpacking District, told from the perspective
of transgender sex workers who lived and worked there.
Filmmaker Kristen Lovell, who walked “The Stroll” for a decade, reunites her community to recount the violence,
policing, homelessness, and gentrification they overcame to build a movement for transgender rights.
Self, played by Kristen Parker Lovell.
Self, played by Ceyenne Doroshow.
Self, played by Egyptt LaBeija.
Self, played by Izzi “Cashmere” Starz.
Self, played by Tabytha Gonzalez.
Self, played by Stefanie Rivera.
The Stroll is a 2023 American documentary film, directed
by Kristen Lovell and Zackary Drucker.
The film documents trans history in New York City, from the perspective of Black and Latina trans women who had been
sex workers in the Meatpacking District during the 1980s and 1990s, in an area known as The Stroll.
The film had its world premiere at the 2023 Sundance Film Festival on January
23, 2023 and won a special jury prize for clarity of vision.
HBO released the film on June 21, 2023.
The film explores themes of new york city, lgbt, sex work, transgender.